RG 079:005, Department of Environmental Protection: Air, Waste and Water
Connecticut State Library
- Series 14. Bureau of Water Management, 1920-1979
  - Permitting, Enforcement, and Remediation Division, 1928-1979; bulk 1969-1977
    - Reports, 1997-051
      - New Haven (Box 16)
        - New Haven Harbor Ecological Studies for UI - Annual Report, 1973 July (Box 17)
        - New Haven Harbor Hydrographic Study Program for UI, 1970 December (Box 17)
        - Cole Works Ecological Monitoring Studies - Annual Report, 1974 May (Box 17)
        - Cole Works Ecological Monitoring Studies - Interim Report, 1974 June (Box 17)
        - New Haven Harbor Station Ecological Monitoring Studies, 1976 June (Box 17)
        - New Haven Harbor Station Ecological Monitoring Studies, 1975 June (Box 17)
        - Coke Works Project Ecological Monitoring Program - Raw Data, 1975 July-December (Box 17)
        - United Illuminating English Station (Maps) (Box 18)
        - Coke Works NPDES Submittals (Box 18)
        - UI NPDES Materials for DEP (Box 18)
        - New Haven Harbor Ecological Studies - Summary Report, 1970-1977 (Box 18)
        - New Haven Harbor Ecological Monitoring Studies - Annual Report, 1978 June; 2 reports (Box 18)
        - New Haven Harbor Ecological Monitoring Studies - Annual Report, 1977 July; 2 reports (Box 18)
        - Thermal Surveys New Haven Harbor for UI, 1976 summer & fall (Box 18)
        - New Haven Harbor Station Ecological Monitoring Studies for UI-Acute Toxicity Studies, 1976 December; 2 reports (Box 18)
        - English Station, UI (Box 19)
        - Ecological Consideration of the Coke Works Site (Box 19)
        - New Haven Harbor Station Ecological Studies for UI, 1976 December (Box 19)
        - New Haven Harbor Station Ecological Monitoring Studies for UI, 1978 June (Box 19)
        - UI Coke Works Project Ecological Monitoring Program - Raw Data, 1973 (Box 19)
        - UI Coke Works Project Ecological Monitoring Program - Raw Data, 1974 January-1974 June (Box 19)
        - UI Coke Works Project Ecological Monitoring Program - Raw Data, 1974 June-December (Box 19)
        - UI Coke Works Project Ecological Monitoring Program - Raw Data, 1975 January-1975 June (Box 19)
        - UI New Haven Harbor Station Ecological Monitoring Studies Raw Data, 1976 January-1976 June (Box 19)
        - Coke Works Site - study of the effect of plant capacities and cooling water discharge (Box 20)
        - locations on the temperature distribution in New Haven Harbor, United Illuminating, New Haven, circa 1970; 2 copies (Box 20)
        - United Illuminating, New Haven Harbor Station (Box 20)
          - Volume I, 1976 July-1976 December (Box 20)
          - Volume II, 1976 January-June 1976 (Box 20)
          - Volume II, 1976 July-1976 December (Box 20)
        - United Illuminating, New Haven Harbor hydrographic study program, 1970 (Box 20)
        - United Illuminating, New Haven Harbor, Ecological Survey, 1970 June-November (Box 20)
        - Winter Report, 1970 December-1971 April (Box 20)
        - Ecological & Hydrological program for New Haven Harbor, 1970 (Box 20)
        - United Illuminating, New Haven Harbor, 1972 January (Box 20)
      - New Milford (Box 21)
        - Industrial Water Treatment System -- Burndy Corp., Candlewood Plant, 1967 March 31 (Box 21)
        - Process Waste Treatment & Disposal at the Maggi Division Plant -- The Nestle Company, Inc., 1967 October 16 (Box 21)
        - Preliminary Engineering Report -- Diventco Company, 1968 February 27 (Box 21)
        - Process Waste Treatment & Disposal at the Maggi Division Plant -- The Nestle Company, Inc., 1972 January 14; 2 copies (Box 21)
        - Design Outline, Wastewater Treatment Additions -- Kimberly-Clark Corporation, 1975 April 21 (Box 21)
        - Report on Process Waste Disposal -- Kimberly-Clark Corporation, 1969 January (Box 21)
        - Waste Treatment Facilities, Project Summary -- Kimberly Clark Corporation, 1970 March 31 (Box 21)
      - Newington (Box 21)
        - Eng. Report. for Industrial Pre-Treatment Facilities -- Atrax Company, 1968 December; 2 copies (Box 21)
        - Proposed Wastewater Treatment Facilities -- Fafnir Bearing Company, 1975 February (Box 21)
        - Water Pollution Control System -- Fafnir Bearing, 1974 May 2 (Box 21)
        - Order No. 1587 Heavy Metals Removal -- Fafnir Bearing, 1975 February 2 (Box 21)
        - Order No. 1587 Oil & Grease Removal -- Fafnir Bearing, 1975 August 5 (Box 21)
        - Eng. Report. on Industrial Waste Treatment -- Keeney Mfg. Co., 1973 October 4; 2 copies (Box 21)
        - Specs. for Wastewater Treatment Facilities -- Keeney Mfg. Co., 1974 July 1 (Box 21)
        - Industrial Waste Treatment System specs. -- Keeney Mfg. Co., 1975 February 13 (Box 21)
        - Industrial Waste Treatment System specs. -- Keeney Mfg. Co., 1975 April 22 (Box 21)
      - North Canaan (Box 21)
        - Construction Plans & Specs, Order No. 819 Step B -- Pfizer Inc., 1970 July 27 (Box 21)
      - North Haven (Box 21)
        - Modifications to the Marlin Firearms Industrial Waste Treatment Facility, 1973 February 21 (Box 21)
        - Eng. Report. on Industrial Waste Treatment Facility -- Marlin Firearms, 1972 March 14; 2 copies (Box 21)
        - Review of N.P.D.E.S. 1981 Draft Permit for North Haven Plant -- Pratt & Whitney, 1971 September 15 (Box 21)
        - Industrial Waste Treatment Facilities -- Pratt & Whitney, 1970 January 23 (Box 21)
        - Industrial Waste Treatment -- Pratt & Whitney, 1968 October 28 (Box 21)
        - Sludge Dewatering Facility -- Pratt & Whitney, 1978 April 24 (Box 21)
        - Preliminary Eng. Report. on Proposed Wastewater Treatment Facilities --- Upjohn Co., 1975 March 10 (Box 21)
        - Study of Alternatives, Muddy River Interceptor and Section V Sewers, Town of North Haven, 1975 January 29 (Box 21)
        - Pollution Control System -- Branford Wire & Mfg. Co., 1974 December 3 (Box 21)
        - Real Estate Appraisal for State of CT, DOT -- Knudsen Brothers Dairy, Inc., 1974 January 9 (Box 21)
      - Norwalk (Box 22)
        - Plans & Specs (5) King Industries (Box 22)
        - King Industries Inc. - Inventory of waste producing processes & location of all drains on property, 1967 August (Box 22)
        - King Industries Inc. - Investigation & verification of Industrial waste going to treatment facilities, 1967 November (Box 22)
        - Kind Industries Inc. - Waste treatment for discharge to the Norwalk River at tidewater for organic chemicals (Box 22)
        - APM - Chemical Co. - Specification (Bethel) pretreatment facilities, 1968 (Box 22)
        - Kings Industries - Pollution Control Program, 1979 March (Box 22)
        - Kings Industries - Stormwater Drainage & Spec Plan, 1979 January (Box 22)
        - Yankee Metal Prod. Corp. - Preliminary Engineering Report - Plating Waste Pollution Abatement Program, 1976 April; 2 reports (Box 22)
        - Yankee Metal Prod Corp. - Drawings for Plating Waste PAP - Plans & Specs, 1976 March (Box 22)
        - Yankee Metal Prod Corp. - Drawings for Plating Waste PAP - Plans & Specs, 1976 April (Box 22)
        - Kings Ind. - disposal of solid waste, 1978 July (Box 22)
        - CL&P - Norwalk Harbor Station - thermal Plume Studies, 1975 December (Box 22)
      - Norwich (Box 23)
        - Lightolier Waste Treatment Design and Sludge Disposal documents (Box 23)
        - Eng. Report. Cooling Water Separation -- United Metal of CT, 1975 October 1 (Box 23)
        - Comprehensive Sewerage Study -- Norwich Hospital, 1977 March 28; 3 copies (Box 23)
        - Sewerage System Study -- Uncas-on-Thames Hospital, 1973 February 23 (Box 23)
        - Report. on the Domestic & Industrial Wastewaters -- Chambers Storck Company, 1968 September (Box 23)
        - Final Engineering Report -- Chambers Storck Company, 1976 December 8 (Box 23)
        - Original Engineering Report -- Chambers Storck Company, 1975 March 17 (Box 23)
      - Old Saybrook (Box 23)
        - Detailed Specifications for Waste Treatment Facility -- Black Swan Marine Corp., 1973 February; 2 copies (Box 23)
        - Concept Eng. Report. -- Conrac Corporation, 1979 June (Box 23)
        - Supplementary Information -- Conrac Corp., 1979 July 30 (Box 23)
        - P & S for Industrial Wastewater Treatment Modifications -- Conrac Corp., 1980 September (Box 23)
        - Industrial Waste Treatment Plant -- Giannini Controls Corp., 1964 October 7 (Box 23)
        - Preliminary Report. for Sanitary Sewage Treatment Facilities, Black Swan Marina, 1972 July (Box 23)
        - Subsurface Sewage Treatment & Disposal System -- R.R. Donnelly & Sons, 1977 December 1 (Box 23)
      - Plainfield (Box 23)
        - Comprehensive Study of the Industrial Wastes Generated at the Moosup Plant with Recommendations for Treatment and Handling -- Kaman Aircraft, 1969 February; 3 copies (Box 23)
        - Evaluation of a Chemical Waste Disposal Area, Tarbox Road Site, 1979 January 29 (Box 23)
        - Plans (3 sets) -- International Hydronics Corporation, 1972 April 21, 1972 July 13, 1972 July 13 (Box 23)
      - Plainville (Box 23)
        - Site Evaluation and Operation Plan for Municipal Sanitary LF, 1977 April (Box 23)
        - Evaluation of Waste Treatment System -- Custom Plating, 1973 November 6 (Box 23)
        - Industrial Waste Treatment Facilities -- Forestville Plating Company, 1965 June (Box 23)
        - Preliminary Eng. Report. for Upgrading WWT -- General Electri, 1974 September 20 (Box 23)
        - Final Eng. Report. -- Gulf Metal Specialties, Inc., Div. of Circle F Ind., 1967 November 30 (Box 23)
        - Eng. Report. on Industrial Waste Treatment (Box 23)
        - Interim Report - Study to Determine an Acceptable Method of Liquid Waste Disposal -- Marlin-Rockwell Division - TRW, 1977 January; 2 copies (Box 23)
        - Final Eng. Report. -- Marlin-Rockwell Corporation, 1973 March 15; 3 copies (Box 23)
        - Preliminary Draft - Final Report - Study to Determine an Acceptable Method of Liquid Waste Disposal -- Marlin-Rockwell Division - TRW, 1977 June (Box 23)
        - Preliminary Eng. Report. -- Marlin Rockwell Corporation, 1972 November 7; 2 copies (Box 23)
        - Plainville Electroplating/Plainville - Preliminary Engineering Industrial Water Treatment System, 1967 September (Box 24)
        - Gull Metal Specialties, Inc./Plainville - Engineering Report Preliminary Ind. Waste treatment Systems, 1966 November (Box 24)
        - Plainville Electroplating/Plainville - Final Engineering Report - Industrial Waste Treatment System, 1968 February (Box 24)
      - Pomfret (Box 24)
        - Idle Wild Farm/Pomfret - Proposed Industrial Waste Water Treatment Facility, 1976 August (Box 24)
        - New London County Courthouse/Pomfret - Site & Utilities Feasibility Cost & Study, 1977 February (Box 24)
      - Putnam (Box 24)
        - Wyckoff Steel/Putnam - Preliminary Engineering Report - Industrial Waste Treatment Report, 1968 May (Box 24)
        - Wyckoff Steel/Putnam - Final Engineering Report, 1969 (Box 24)
      - Ridgefield (Box 24)
        - Benrus Watch Co./Ridgefield - Preliminary survey Industrial Waste Treatment, 1965 April (Box 24)
        - Benrus Watch Co./Ridgefield - Specification for Phase No., 1966 September (Box 24)
        - Benrus Watch Co./Ridgefield - Industrial Waste Treatment System, 1966 September (Box 24)
        - Kerete Co./Ridgefield - Specifications, 1972 June; 2 copies (Box 24)
        - Kerete Co./Ridgefield - Preliminary Report & Specs, 1971 July (Box 24)
      - Salisbury (Box 24)
        - The Salisbury Assoc./Salisbury-Hydrologics/Nutrient Budget Study, 1977 June (Box 24)
      - Seymour (Box 24)
        - Pond’s Extract Co./Seymour - White Water System, 1938 October-1938 November (Box 24)
      - Shelton (Box 24)
        - B.F. Goodrich Sponge Product Division/Shelton - WPCF for Washwater Waste, 1970 May (Box 24)
        - B.F. Goodrich Sponge Product Division/Shelton-Supplementary Report-Lime Treatment of Washwater Waste, 1970 March (Box 24)
        - B.F. Goodrich Sponge Product Division/Shelton - Latex Waste Studies, 1967 May (Box 24)
        - Driscoll wire Co./Shelton - Report on Industrial Wastes, 1968 September (Box 24)
        - Chromium Process Corp./Shelton - Report for Industrial Waste Treatment System, 1966 October & 1967 August; 2 copies (Box 24)
        - The Star Pin Co./Shelton - Final Engineering Report, 1963 December & 1968 August & 1970 August (Box 24)
        - USM/Fastener Division/Shelton-Preliminary Engineering Report-Indus Waste Treatment System & plans, 1972 November & 1973 February (Box 24)
        - Empire State Novelty CO/Shelton- Preliminary Report Indus Waste Treatment System & Specs, 1969 March & 1970 March (Box 24)
      - Somers (Box 24)
        - AAB Platers - Report on Pollution Cont. Facility/Somers with supplementary Letters, 1968 June & 1968 August (Box 24)
        - Somers Industrial Finishing Corp./Somers - Specifications for Industrial Waste Treatment System, 1978 February (Box 24)
        - Somers Plating/Somers - Modifications on Waste Treatment Facility, 1977 February (Box 24)
        - Somers Industrial Finishing Corp./Somers Report, 1975 May (Box 24)
        - Somers Industrial Finishing Corp. Specifications/Somers, 1975 October & 1977 May & 1978 February (Box 24)
        - Somers Plating/Somers - Report on Proposed Waste Disposal Facilities, 1966 August (Box 24)
        - AAB Platers/Somers - operational procedures for batch treatment of plating wastewater, 1971 November (Box 24)
      - Southbury (Box 25)
        - Baskin-Robbins, Southbury, May 1971 (2 copies), Aug. 1976, Aug. 1975, May 1971 (appendix A) (2 copies), Dec. 1969, Apr. 1970, Jul. 1970 (Box 25)
        - Foremost Dairy, Inc., Southbury, 1959 (Box 25)
        - Dolly Madison Industries, Inc., Southbury, 1968 (Box 25)
      - Southington (Box 25)
        - The Beaton & Corbin Mfg. Co., Southington, 1968 (Box 25)
        - Screw & Bolt Corp. Of America, Southington, 1966 (Box 25)
        - Report to Board of Water Commissioners, Southington on Construction of Well No. 6, 1976 (Box 25)
        - Rex Forge Division, The Connrex Corp., Plantsville, 1966, 1968 (Box 25)
        - Allied Control Co. Inc., Plantsville, 1966, 1972, 1972 May, 1971 July (Box 25)
        - Southington Hardware Division, Modulus Corp., Southington, 1969, 1971 (Box 25)
        - Davco, Division of Davis Industries, 1971-1972 (Box 25)
        - Study of Ground-Water Contamination Problem, Southington, 1969; 2 copies (Box 25)
        - Pratt & Whitney Aircraft, United Aircraft, Southington, 1969, 1970 (Box 25)
        - Solvents Recovery Service of New England, Inc., Southington, 1979; 3 copies (Box 25)
        - Screw & Bolt Division, Modulus Corp., Southington, 1968 (Box 25)
      - Sprague (Box 25)
        - Federal Paper Board Co. Inc., Sprague, 1978 June, 1978 October, 1978 October revised, 1979 (Box 25)
        - M.S. Chambers & Sons, Inc., Baltic, 1972 February, 1972 June; 2 copies (Box 25)
      - Stafford (Box 26)
        - Tech Specs for a Water Pollution Control Facility at North American Printed Circuits, Stafford, 1976 August (Box 26)
      - Stamfod (Box 26)
        - Report to OZ Gedney Co., Terryville on Additions or Mod to Existing Wastewater Treatment Facilities, 1978 March (Box 26)
        - Report on Biological Treatability of the Industries Waste stream of the Stamford Facility, Clairol Inc., 1978 March (Box 26)
        - Clairol Inc., Stamford, Chemical Pretreatment Facilities, Purchase Specs., 1977 September (Box 26)
        - Engineering Report - Proposed Pretreatment Facilities for Clairol, Inc., Stamford, 1977 May (Box 26)
        - Proposed Aerator draft lube repairs for the Stamford Sewage Treatment Plant, 1977 October (Box 26)
        - Machlett Laboratories, Inc., Chemical Waste Treatment System Report (Box 26)
        - Report OX Gedney Co., Terryville on Additions or Modifications to Existing Wastewater Treatment Facilities, 1974 July (Box 26)
        - Results of Waste Water Survey and Recommended Waste Treatment Facilities for Cero Copper and Brass Co., Stamford, 1969 February (Box 26)
        - Clairol Treatability Study Progress Report I, 1977 March (Box 26)
        - A Report on the Characterization and Treatment of Industrial Wastewater for Clairol, Inc., 1975 November (Box 26)
        - Operation, Management, and Engineering. Plans for a proposed Sanitary Landfill - Kement, Suffield, 1976 August (Box 26)
        - Preliminary Report and Plans - American Cysloscope Makers, Inc., Stamford on Industrial Waste Water Treatment of New Metal Finishing Operation Mar. 1978, 1978 March (Box 26)
      - Sterling (Box 26)
        - Report to Renere Textile Prints Co., Sterling on Process Wastewater Treatment & disposal, 1977 August (Box 26)
      - Stonington (Box 26)
        - Supplemental Environmental Assessment Statement Stonington Lateral Sewers, Stonington, 1977 July (Box 26)
        - Draft Report on Industrial Wastewater Treatment for American Velvent Co., Stonington, 1977 December (Box 26)
        - Report on Industrial Wastewater Treatment for American Velvet Co., Stonington, CT, 1978 May (Box 26)
      - Storrs (Box 26)
        - Soils & foundations Report, Sewage Treatment Plans Expansion, Univ. Of CT, Storrs, 1972 June (Box 26)
        - Infiltration/Inflow Study - Phase /Analysis - UCONN, Storrs, 1973 February; 2 copies (Box 26)
        - Flow Verification Study at UCONN Sewage Treatment Plant, Storrs, 1973 February (Box 26)
      - Stamford (Box 26)
        - Study & Report of the Chemical Waste Treatment Plant at Pitney Bowes, Inc. Facility, Stamford, 1975 August (Box 26)
        - Report on Machlett Laboratories, Inc., Stamford on Industrial Waste Treatment System, 1962 July (Box 26)
        - Preliminary Engineering Report Industrial Waste Treatment System - Machlett Laboratories, Inc., Stamford, 1971 August (Box 26)
        - Preliminary Report - Pitney-Bowes, Inc., Stamford, CT, 1971 June (Box 26)
        - Study & Report of the Chemical Waste Treatment Plant at Pitney Bowes Inc. Facility, Stamford, 1975 August (Box 26)
        - Pitney Bowes - Black Oxide Plans, 1972 December (Box 26)
        - Engineering Report Treatment of Metal Finishing Waste Research Plating & Electroforming Corp., Stamford, 1976 January (Box 26)
      - Stratford (Box 26)
        - Preliminary Report on Collection & Pumping System for AVCO - Lycoming Division, Stratford, 1971 October; 2 reports (Box 26)
        - Report on Oil Bearing Wastewater, AVCO-Lycoming Div., Stratford, 1971 July (Box 26)
        - Contract Plans & Specs for required treatment facilities, Raybestos-Manhattan, Inc. Stratford, 1969 May (Box 26)
        - Engineering Report to Raybestos-Manhattan, Stratford on Proposed Water Pollution Control Measures, 1972 April (Box 26)
        - Report for Raybestos Division of Raybestos-Manhattan, Inc., Stratford - Plans & Specs for Construction of Acid Neutralization Plant, 1972 September (Box 26)
        - Engineering Report of sources & volumes of industrial wastes from Raybestos Division, Stratford, 1969 January (Box 26)
        - Preliminary Report on Waste Disposal - Contract Plating Co., Stratford, 1960 March (Box 26)
        - Waste Disposal Report - Contract Plating Co., Stratford, 1960 may (Box 26)
        - Process Specs for Internal Waste Treatment Control for Contract Plating Co., Stratford, 1960 November (Box 26)
        - Engineering Report to Contract Plating Co., Stratford on Propose automation of Industrial Waste Treatment Facilities, 1968 August (Box 26)
        - Specs for Chemical Feed and Control Equipment for Contract Plating Co., Stratford, CT, 1969 January (Box 26)
        - Waste Chemical, Stratford - Proposal to Discharge Retreated Equipment Washwater to Town of Stratford Sewage Works, 1979 October (Box 26)
        - Engineering Report - Industrial Wastewater Pretreatment System Cooperlite Corp., Stratford, 1978 June (Box 26)
        - Engineering Report - Industrial Wastewater Pretreatment System - Micro-etch Products, Stratford, 1978 April (Box 26)
        - Report for Raybestos Manhattan, Inc. Stratford - Plans & Specs for Construction of Rehnol Waste Incinerator with plans, 1972 September; 2 reports (Box 26)
        - Engineering Report - Raybestos Manhattan, Stratford on Proposed Water Pollution Control, 1972 April 28 (Box 26)
        - Engineering Report - Raybestos Division, Raybestos Manhattan, Inc. Stratford - Plans & Specs for construction of Acid Neutralization Plant, 1972 September (Box 26)
        - Chemical Plating Co., - Plans & Specs (Box 26)
        - Chemical Plating Co., - Rpts, 1968-1969 (Box 26)
        - Report to the Lycoming Division - ARCO Manufacturing Corp., Stratford, CT on Industrial Waste Treatment Plant, 1955 June (Box 27)
        - Combined Industrial Wastewater & Stormwater Treatment considerations and conceptual Engineering. Design ARCO Lycoming Div., Stratford, CT, 1971 December (Box 27)
        - Part VI, Section V, Disposal of Oily Waste (2) with plans, Rev., 1972 May 10 (Box 27)
        - Contract Documents & Specifications for Construction of Waste Collection and Treatment Oil Abatement Project for ARCO Lycoming Div., 550 So. Main St., Stratford, 1971 December (Box 27)
        - Engineering Report to Contract Plating Co., Stratford - Modifications to Existing Industrial Waste Treatment Facilities, 1973 January (Box 27)
        - Evaluation Report on the Pollution Control Program at Chemical Plating Co., Stratford, 1978 November (Box 27)
        - Specs for Modifications to Existing Industrial Waste Treatment Facilities at Contract Plating Co., Inc. Stratford, 1978 March (Box 27)
        - Specs for Modifications to Existing Waste Treatment Facilities for Contract Plating Co., Stratford, 1973 September (Box 27)
        - Quotation LT-179, Lamella Thickener for Contract Plating, Stratford, 1973 September (Box 27)
        - Progress Report on Elimination of Phenols from Plant Effluent for Raybestos Manhattan Friction Materials Co., Stratford, 1975 November; 2 reports (Box 27)
        - Interim Report on Elimination of Phenols from Plant Effluent for Raybestos Manhattan Friction Materials Co., Stratford, 1976 July (Box 27)
        - Phase II Report on Elimination of Phenols from Plant Effluent for Raybestos Manhattan Friction Materials Co., Stratford, 1976 December (Box 27)
      - Thomaston (Box 27)
        - The Doret Corp., No Main St., Thomaston - Waste Management Program Order #264, Step B, Plans & Specifications, 1970 April (Box 27)
        - Evaluation Report of the pollution abatement facilities at Whyco Chromium Co., Thomaston, 1974 May (Box 27)
        - Report to Tech Systems Corp., 401 Watertown Road, Thomaston on Industrial Wastewater Treatment Facilities, 1975 March (Box 27)
        - Whyco Chromium Co., Waterbury Road, Thomaston - Water & Waste Management Preliminary Report, 1969 October (Box 27)
        - Donham Craft, Inc. 4 River St., Thomaston, - Water & Waste Management Preliminary Survey Report, 1968 October (Box 27)
        - Donham Craft, Inc., Thomaston - Waste Management Program Order #267, Step B, Plans & Speculations, 1970 January (Box 27)
        - Rinse Tank Control System (Box 27)
        - Operating Manual, Pfaudler Chrome Recovery System for Whyco Chromium Co., Thomaston, 1970 October (Box 27)
        - Engineering Report Summit Finishing Division, Kawecki Berylco Indus., Inc., 1430 Waterbury Road, Thomaston, 1977 October (Box 27)
        - Final Engineering. Report - Summit Finishing Div. - The Beryllium Corp. Thomaston, 1969 July (Box 27)
        - Preliminary Engineering Report - Summit Finishing Div. - The Beryllium Corp. Thomaston, 1968 October (Box 27)
        - Donham Craft, Inc. 4 River St., Thomaston - Water & Waste Program Preliminary Survey Addendum, 1969 April (Box 27)